tettra.co 2017-11-15

# Privacy Policy | Tettra

At Tettra, we are all about transparency. In order to keep our commitment to transparency, you’ll find our Privacy Policy in full below. We ask you to read it thoroughly and contact us if you have any questions. But… let’s be honest… This type of stuff is usually pretty boring, so it’s a safe bet that you won’t read it thoroughly, so here are the highlights and important bits:

  1. Tettra connects to your Slack account and displays your content in a wiki-style format. We access the content of your account through the Slack API.
  2. We don’t store the content of your Slack messages, files and comments or data about your team, except for a few key pieces of information we use to improve the product and provide support. The data we collect is limited to: 
    1. Your full name, email address and Slack user id
    2. Your Slack company name, team URL and team id
    3. Various usage data in Google Analytics, Amplitude and Intercom which we use to provide support, improve the product and just generally make better decisions so our startup doesn’t fail.
  3. We will never use the access tokens you authorize to Tettra via the Slack API to read your content.
  4. You can revoke Tettra’s access to your Slack account at any time by going to[yourteam.slack.com/apps/manage](http://yourteam.slack.com/apps/manage), choosing the “Tettra” app from your list of integrations and then pressing the Remove App button.
  5. Just like all things in life, this privacy policy may change from time to time. We’ll notify you in advance and provide you with alternative options if something doesn’t jive quite right with you.

## Tettra Privacy Policy

Updated: January 13, 2016

This privacy policy is here to help you understand what information we collect at Tettra, how we use it, and what choices you have. When we talk about Tettra in this policy, we are talking about Tettra, Inc., the company and the Tettra website at [tettra.co](http://www.tettra.co/). Tettra is available for use via a web or mobile browser.

This policy describes how Tettra treats your information, not how other organizations or Slack Technologies, Inc. treats your information. If you are using Tettra in a workplace or on a device or account issued to you by your employer or another organization, that company or organization likely has its own policies regarding storage, access, modification, deletion, and retention of communications and content which may apply to your use of Tettra, stored in Slack’s platform. Content that would otherwise be considered private to you or to a limited group of people may, in some cases, be accessible by your team owner or administrator. Please check with your employer, team owner or administrator about the policies it has in place regarding your communications and related content on Tettra. More on this below.

## Information we don’t collect or access

Keeping your data safe and secure is one of our top priorities. The best way to keep your data safe is to not store it on our servers or save the information which would allow us to access your content. Here is the content that we don’t collect about you or your Slack account:

  * **Your content.** We don’t store the content of your direct messages, channels, group conversations or files to our database. In fact, all your data is stored on the existing Slack Platform in your existing Slack account. We only read and write to your account via the Slack API.
  * **Your API tokens.** We don’t store your API tokens on our servers, so our team can’t access or share your data. We store your access tokens in a cookie on your local browser, which you can manage through your browser settings or by revoking the token that Tettra has been authorized to access to your Slack account.

## Information we collect and receive

We collect different kinds of information. Some of it is personally identifiable and some is non-identifying or aggregated. Here are the types of information we collect or receive:

  * **Personal information.** Tettra collects your email addres and full name when you authorized your Slack account via the Slack API.
  * **Billing information.** If you purchase a premium version of Tettra, our third party payment processors will collect and store your billing address and credit card information. We use Stripe.
  * **Log data.** When you use Tettra, our servers automatically record information, including information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This log data may include your Internet Protocol address, the address of the web page you visited before coming to Tettra, your browser type and settings, the date and time of your request, information about your browser configuration and plug-ins, language preferences, and cookie data. Log data does not contain message content and is not routinely deleted.
  * **Device information.** In addition to log data, we may also collect information about the device you’re using Tettra on, including what type of device it is, what operating system you’re using, device settings, unique device identifiers, and crash data. Whether we collect some or all of this information often depends on what type of device you’re using and its settings.
  * **Tettra usage information.** This is information about which features you interact with within Tettra. We don’t log the actual content of the messages, files and comments, just the fact that an event happened using those features on Tettra.

## Cookie policy

Tettra uses cookies, or similar technologies like single-pixel gifs and web beacons, to record log data. We use both session-based and persistent cookies.

Cookies are small text files sent by us to your computer and from your computer to us, each time you visit our website. They are unique to your Tettra account or your browser. Session-based cookies last only while your browser is open and are automatically deleted when you close your browser. Persistent cookies last until you or your browser delete them or until they expire.

Some cookies are associated with your Slack account and personal information in order to remember that you are logged in and which teams you are logged into. Other cookies are not tied to your Tettra account but are unique and allow us to do site analytics and customization, among other similar things. If you access Slack through your browser, you can manage your cookie settings there but if you disable all cookies you may not be able to use Tettra.

Tettra sets and accesses our own cookies on our company-owned domains. In addition, we use 3rd parties like Google Analytics, Intercom and Amplitude for website analytics. You may opt-out of third party cookies from [Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout), [Amplitude](https://amplitude.com/privacy) and Intercom on their respective websites. We do not currently recognize or respond to browser-initiated Do Not Track signals as there is no consistent industry standard for compliance.

## How we use your information

We use your information for the following:

  * **Providing the Tettra service.** We use your Slack API token to display your Slack content in Tettra in a wiki-like format.
  * **Understanding and improving our products**. To make the product better we have to understand how users are using it. We have a fair bit of data about usage and we intend to use it many different ways to improve our products, including research. This policy is not intended to place any limits on what we do with usage data that is aggregated or de-identified so it is no longer tied to a Tettra user.
  * **Investigating and preventing bad stuff from happening.** We work hard to keep Slack secure and to prevent abuse and fraud.
  * **Communicating with you**
    * **Solving your problems and responding to your requests.** If you contact us with a problem or question, we will use your information to respond to that request and address your problems or concerns.
    * **In-product communications.** We may use the information you provide to contact you through in-product messaging tools. For example, if, after, a few weeks of using Tettra we notice that you haven’t posted your company’s vacation policy, we may send you a message that suggests you add that piece of knowledge. This is just one example of how we use information about your usage of the product to make suggestions to you.
    * **Email messages.** We may send you service and administrative emails, such as when we notice that you are nearing a the end of your free trial or over your user limit. We may also contact you to inform you about changes in our services, our service offerings and important service related notices, such as changes to this policy or security and fraud notices. These messages are considered part of the service and you may not opt-out of them. In addition, we sometimes send emails to Tettra users about new product features or other news about Tettra. You can opt-out of these at any time.

## Security and third-party services

Tettra doesn’t store your Slack passwords or access tokens authorized to us via the Slack API. Access to your Slack account is only done through the Slack API.

Tettra operates its app on the [Heroku](http://www.heroku.com/) platform (see <https://www.heroku.com/policy/privacy>)

Tettra encrypts data through an SSL certificate provided by [RapidSSL](http://www.rapidssl.com/) (see[https://www.rapidssl.com/privacy/index.html)](https://www.rapidssl.com/privacy/index.html))

Our team uses [Intercom](http://www.intercom.io/) to provide support for our apps and [Amplitude](https://amplitude.com/) to track usage statistics. We store your full name and email, along with your Slack user id, team id, and team name in both services.

## Policy

This privacy policy may change from time to time, we will notify you.

By continuing to access or use the services provided by Tettra after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

## Advertising

Good news! We don’t display advertisements in any of our products, and we do not share any information with advertisers.
